(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
I'm giddy giddy giddy...
Giddy giddy giddy... Giddy giddy giddy...
Attention ご来場のお客様へ
Attention: To all visitors
演出の都合上、照明の点滅にご注意ください
Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance.
声出し応援OKです
Cheering loudly is OK.
I'm giddy giddy giddy...
受注生産グッズ①
Made-to-order Goods 1
ねぇ 惹かれ合ってしまったの
Hey, we've fallen for each other
誰も触れられない
Nobody can touch it
二人だけの重力の中
In a gravity meant only for the two of us
受注生産グッズ②
Made-to-order Goods 2
さあ さあ さあ 偽物のテンプレな日常を
Come, come, come, break this fake, template everyday life
受注生産グッズ③
Made-to-order Goods 3
壊してしまえよ 今
Break it all down now
受注生産グッズ④
Made-to-order Goods 4
受注生産グッズ⑤
Made-to-order Goods 5
踊りだした ソワレの街
The town of the soirée has begun to dance
明かりが灯るまで
Until the lights come on
あと少しだけ このままで
Stay like this for just a little longer
ビビデバビデブー
Bibbidi-Bobbidi-Boo
魔法も解けたって関係ないや
Even if the magic breaks, it doesn't matter
私は私のまま
I'll stay as myself
だって僕は星だから
Because I am a star
Stellar Stellar
夜を越えて
Beyond the night
連れてってよ
Take me with you
道連れにしてよ
Make me your companion
この先へ
To what lies ahead
何回だって歌うよ
I'll sing it as many times as it takes
届くまで
Until it reaches you
僕はここにいるよ
I am right here
アンドロメダの夜空に
In the Andromeda night sky
手を伸ばして
Reaching out my hand
光を掴むんだ
I'll grab the light
ねぇ 惹かれ合ってしまったの
Hey, we've fallen for each other
誰も触れられない
Nobody can touch it
二人だけの重力の中
In a gravity meant only for the two of us
HOSHIMACHI SUISEI LIVE TOUR 2024
SPECTRA OF NOVA
Attention ご来場のお客様へ
演出の都合上、照明の点滅にご注意ください
声出し応援OKです
Attention: To all attendees
Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance.
Cheering loudly is OK.
Hoshimachi Suisei Live Tour 2024 "Spectra of Nova"
受注生産グッズ
Made-to-order Goods
HOSHIMACHI SUISEI LIVE TOUR 2024
SPECTRA OF NOVA
FUKUOKA SUNPALACE
開演までしばらくお待ちください
HOSHIMACHI SUISEI LIVE TOUR 2024
SPECTRA OF NOVA
FUKUOKA SUNPALACE
The concert will be starting soon.
SPONSORS 協賛
JOYSOUND
ふくや
SPONSORS
JOYSOUND
Fukuya
SPONSORS 協賛
SPONSORS
最近行ったのよ、カラオケ。
I went to karaoke recently.
なんさ、2時間で解散と思うじゃん。
You know, you'd think we'd call it a night after two hours.
そっからなのよ。
But that's when the real fun starts.
え？
Huh?
色んなことできるわけ。ヤバいぞ。
You can do so many things. It's awesome.
PLAY! NEW (X).
X PARK
X PARK最高。
X PARK is the best.
JOYSOUND X1
明太子をつくってよかった。
博多中洲 ふくや
I'm glad I made mentaiko.
Hakata Nakasu Fukuya
ふくや。
Fukuya.
明太子がー！
The mentaiko is...!
切袴？
Kireo?
マコ？
Mako?
姫、明太子が生まれ変わる新しい技を編み出してきました。
Princess, I've devised a new technique that transforms mentaiko.
いきます！
Here I go!
ふくやの明太子から生まれたメンチーズシリーズ。
The Men Cheese series, born from Fukuya's mentaiko.
ピリリな味わい、マコも大好き！
A spicy flavor that Mako loves too!
詳しくはWebで！
Check the web for details!
My name is Clarity Powers and I sing in Sony Pictures projects.
When you fell from the sky, you created quite a buzz for us here.
And this song is much better than anything else I could say.
It's called "Spectra of Nova" off of the album "Stellar Stellar."
開演までしばらくお待ちください
The concert will be starting soon.
Attention
ご来場のお客様へ
To all visitors
演出の都合上、照明の点滅にご注意ください
Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance.
声出し応援OKです
Cheering loudly is OK.
受注生産グッズ①
Essentials Pack
Made-to-order Goods ①
受注生産グッズ②
Light Stick / Towel / T-shirt / Ring Light
Made-to-order Goods ②
受注生産グッズ③
Long-Sleeve T-shirt / Shoulder Bag / Socks
Made-to-order Goods ③
受注生産グッズ④
Pouch Set / Keychain
Made-to-order Goods ④
受注生産グッズ⑤
Acrylic Stand / Tapestry
Made-to-order Goods ⑤
HOSHIMACHI SUISEI LIVE TOUR 2024 "Spectra of Nova"
Attention ご来場の皆様へ
Attention: To all attendees
受注生産グッズ ラインナップ
Made-to-order Goods Lineup
HOSHIMACHI SUISEI LIVE TOUR 2024 "Spectra of Nova"
開演までしばらくお待ちください
The concert will be starting soon.
Attention ご来場のお客様へ
Attention to our guests
演出の都合上、照明の点滅にご注意ください
Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance.
声出し応援OKです
Cheering loudly is OK.
受注生産グッズ ① Essentials Pack
Made-to-order Goods ① Essentials Pack
受注生産グッズ ②
Made-to-order Goods ②
受注生産グッズ ③
Made-to-order Goods ③
受注生産グッズ ④
Made-to-order Goods ④
受注生産グッズ ⑤
Made-to-order Goods ⑤
ワン、ツー。
One, two.
星街すいせいライブツアー
Thank you for coming to
2024 「Spectra of Nova」に
Hoshimachi Suisei Live Tour 2024
ご来場いただきありがとうございます。
"Spectra of Nova."
星街すいせいです。
I'm Hoshimachi Suisei.
最後までライブを楽しんでいただくために、
To ensure everyone enjoys the concert to the very end,
いくつかご案内させていただきます。
I have a few announcements to make.
いい返事。
Good answer.
公演中の撮影、録音、録画機材の使用は
Photography, recording, and the use of filming
固くお断りいたします。
equipment during the performance are strictly prohibited.
万が一具合が悪くなってしまった場合は、
In the event that you start feeling unwell,
無理をせず近くのスタッフへお知らせください。
please do not push yourself and notify a nearby staff member.
会場内でのモッシュ、ダイブ、ステージに物投げ込む、
Mosh, dive, throwing things onto the stage,
もつ鍋を食べる、明太子を食べるなど、
eating motsunabe, eating mentaiko, and so on,
他のみんなの迷惑になったり公演を妨げる行為は
acts that annoy others or disrupt the performance
一切禁止となっております。
are strictly forbidden.
ルールを守って盛り上がってください。
Please follow the rules and let's get excited!
また、
Also,
いい返事。
Good answer.
また、本公演は映像配信および
Additionally, this performance will be streamed and
写真撮影用のカメラが会場内に入り、
cameras for photography will be present in the venue,
客席が映り込む場合がございます。
and the audience may be captured in the footage.
これらの映像や写真はプロモーションなどに
These videos and photos may be used for
使用される可能性がございますので、
promotional purposes and such,
あらかじめご了承ください。
so please be aware of this in advance.
元気。
You're energetic.
また、ライブのハッシュタグは #かけ巡る星街 です。
Also, the hashtag for the live is #かけ巡る星街.
ハッシュタグを使ってたくさん盛り上げてください。
Please use the hashtag and spread the excitement!
すいちゃんは〜？
Suichan is...?
今日もかわいい！
Always cute today too!
ありがとう！ それでは開演までもう少しです。
Thank you! Well, it's almost time to start.
みんなで一緒に盛り上がりましょう！
Let's all get excited together!
イェーイ！
Yay!
またあとで！
See you later!
Are you ready?
HOSHIMACHI SUISEI LIVE TOUR 2024
SPECTRA of NOVA
福岡の声、聞かせてください！
Let me hear you, Fukuoka!
ヘイ！ヘイ！ヘイ！ヘイ！
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
本音も建前も
Your true feelings and your facade...
駆け引き上手な大人になんて
To becoming an adult skilled in mind games...
そんな言葉信用できない
I can't trust words like those.
できない
I can't.
運命で片付けて
Brush it off as destiny...
進化し続ける手口伝えて
And show me the tricks of how you keep evolving.
人肌の温もり
The warmth of human skin.
ねえ、このままずっと
Hey, it stays like this forever...
降り止まない雨の世界だ
A world where the rain never stops falling.
もう悲しくない
I'm not sad anymore...
人は堕れる生き物だから
Because humans are creatures that fall.
空白になった
Just turning a page...
青春の1ページめくるだけ
Of a youth that has become blank.
今、君に会いたいと
Right now, I want to see you so much...
涙こみ上げる
The tears are welling up.
踏んだり蹴ったり注意散漫人生の
In a life full of misfortune and distraction...
...のようだ
...Like a
嵐 地鳴り乗りこなしていくんだ
I'll ride through the storms and the tremors
透明で
Transparent
鮮明で
Vivid
叫び声あげる前
Before letting out a scream
泥塗れ
Covered in mud
失敗し転がっていくの
Failing and tumbling down
このままずっと降りやまない雨の世界だ
In this world of never-ending rain
愛するしかない それしかない 昨日じゃないから
There's nothing but to love, only that, for it's not yesterday
白紙になった青春の何ページ目だったっけ
What page was it of my youth that turned blank?
忘れ物 思い出せないまま
Still unable to remember what I've forgotten
忘れないよ このままじゃ
I won't forget, not like this
ねえ このままずっと降りやまない雨の世界だ
Hey, in this world of never-ending rain
もう許すしかない 人になれる生き物だから
There's nothing left but to forgive, since we're creatures that can become human
白紙になった青春の何ページ目だったっけ
What page was it of my youth that turned blank?
いま君に会いたいと 涙こらえて
Holding back tears, wanting to see you now
さよならだ さよならだって 認めたくないけど
It's goodbye, it's goodbye, although I don't want to admit it
雨上がりのこの世界が 眩しいから
Because this world after the rain is so dazzling
もう帰らない 振り返らない 思い出とともに
I won't go back, I won't look back, together with the memories
新しい風になれ そしてまた君に
Become a new wind, and once again, to you...
会いたいと願い 駆けていく
Wishing to see you, I'll run...
駆けていく
I'll run...
空っぽな財布 凍えた叙情
An empty wallet, frozen lyricism
ガラクタ透けた 逃げ場所なんて見た
Junk showed through, I saw a place like an escape
どんな言葉にも ちゃんと語尾があったのに
もう今は土に遊ぼう
Every word used to have a proper ending
But now let's play in the dirt
どうでもいい朝になれすぎて
Getting too used to mornings that don't matter
傘を持ってない 借りてた未来
I don't have an umbrella, for the future I borrowed
乾ききった喉 乾ききった殻 街行くよそもの
A parched throat, a parched shell, a stranger walking through the town
ねえ独りだ 飾ってたのは Maybe rainy, rainy
Hey, I'm alone, what I was decorating was "Maybe rainy, rainy"
君を待っていたの rainy
I was waiting for you, rainy
悲しくはないよ 嬉しくもないよ Maybe rainy, rainy
It's not sad, it's not happy either, Maybe rainy, rainy
汚れきった日々に
In the days that have become completely filthy
原色式の細路地染める rainy, rainy
Dyeing the narrow alleys in primary colors, rainy, rainy
こんな間違いだらけ rainy
So full of mistakes, rainy
塗りつぶしていく パノラマ rainy, rainy
Painting over the panorama, rainy, rainy
君を待っていたの Bye-bye
I was waiting for you, Bye-bye
Bye-bye 汚れきった日々の賞賛
Bye-bye, praise for the days that have become completely filthy
真昼の感情は 案内役は置いて
Midday emotions, leaving the guide behind
光当たった それでよかった
The light hit, and that was good enough
泣いて 泣いて 泣いて 涙が枯れ果てた
Crying, crying, crying until my tears ran dry
使い捨ての命は回したくないな
I don't want to spin this disposable life
喧騒興奮の ざわめき声 夢中同盟
The rustling voices of bustle and excitement, an alliance in a trance
白い煙に巻かれながら歌う 救いのない世迷い事
Singing while enveloped in white smoke, words of no salvation
ねえ独りだ 綻ばせたのは Maybe rainy, rainy
Hey, I'm alone, what I caused to fray was "Maybe rainy, rainy"
君を待っていたの Maybe...
I was waiting for you, Maybe...
いつか声に似ている方にお別れ
One day, I'll say goodbye to that voice that resembles mine
バイバイ　バイバイ　しなくちゃいけないんだ
Bye-bye, bye-bye, I have to do it
ほんの僅かに雨の間に間に
In just a tiny bit of the rain's interval
君の行く末を祈ってる
I pray for your future
ねえ一人で戦ったのは ベイビーベイビー君と出会うために
Hey, the reason I fought alone, baby, baby, was to meet you
悲しくはないよ 嬉しくもないよ ベイビーベイビーよく晴れてベイビーベイビー
It's not sad, it's not happy either, baby, baby, the weather's fine, baby, baby
幻想曲の舗装を埋めるレイニーレイニー恋をしたんだね
Filling the pavement of the fantasia, rainy, rainy, you fell in love, didn't you?
メリースピーカーパノラマレイニーレイニー君が待ってたよ
Merry speaker panorama, rainy, rainy, you were waiting
バイバイ　バイバイ　よく晴れてベイビーベイビー　バイバイ
Bye-bye, bye-bye, the weather's fine, baby, baby, bye-bye
しなやかでアン・ドゥ・トロワ 似たようなあざむ手
Supplely, un, deux, trois; similar deceiving hands
まるで違わ 交差する星彩
Just like different, crossing starlight
新しく目覚めるデジャヴを待つぜ
Waiting for a newly awakening déjà vu
駆け抜けるストーリー テレパシー惑わす
The story runs through, confusing telepathy
私はダメ 朝日の下騒げる
I'm no good, making a fuss under the morning sun
何を信じる？ Oh-oh
What do you believe? Oh-oh
眩しくて反らした初期衝動今更通知して
Dazzled, I turned away my primal urge, now notify me
虚ろな愛の引力を抱いて
Hold onto the void gravity of love
聞き飽きてきたでしょうが？
You've grown tired of hearing it, haven't you?
完成度のダンスさ
It's a dance of perfection
退屈してるんじゃない？ I'm ready to dance!
Aren't you bored? I'm ready to dance!
千載一遇のニューセンスでさあ謳歌
With a once-in-a-lifetime new sense, let's enjoy
交差のシンパシーで Wow-wow
With crossing sympathy, Wow-wow
若干主義のイノセンスでさあ謳歌
With a bit of principled innocence, let's enjoy
奇跡の世界も自分次第ね
A world of miracles is also up to you
Satzの革命の狼煙は
The signal fire of Satz's revolution is...
さあ不変の 変化を恐れない覚悟を
Now, be prepared not to fear change
蓄えて大地を駆け抜けよういつかの光
Store it up and run through the earth, the light from someday
変わりたい 変えたいの連鎖が
A chain of wanting to change, wanting to be changed
剥き出しの私を抱きしめる
Embraces my bare self
一千万年一度の霧のサプライズで ロマンチックなキスにしよう
With a once-in-ten-million-years mist surprise, let's make it a romantic kiss
変化！
Change!
アイソラニーに賭けた 遠すぎる欠片
Bet on Isolany, fragments too far away
放速を越え魅せられたい
I want to be enchanted, exceeding the speed of release
惑星が散りばめられた
Planets were scattered
What do you need? What do you take? 望む場所へさあ Go go go!
What do you need? What do you take? To the place you desire, go, go, go!
望んだ夢をただ謳歌 不透明な空を拝啓じゃ
Just enjoy the dream you wished for, against the backdrop of an opaque sky
煌めきを銀河の果てで Catch me now!
Catch the sparkle at the edge of the galaxy, catch me now!
星を読めたつもりの幻覚じゃ
With the hallucination of having read the stars
ちゃんとその五感で確かめて Show me!
Make sure with those five senses, show me!
モニター越しの輝きじゃつまんない
Sparkle through a monitor is boring
飛び出す音鳴るコンプレックスへ
Into the popping, sounding complex
Hey! 目を逸らさず見ててよね
Hey! Keep your eyes on me
自由を得れば
If I gain freedom
踏み出した切ない僕に告げて やって
Tell the sad me who stepped forward
希望も絶望も自分次第ね
Both hope and despair are up to you
Satzの革命の火蓋は
The start of Satz's revolution is...
さあ覚悟 変化を望む感情を
Now, prepare the emotion that desires change
奮い立て心に満ちた至近光の光
Stir it up, the light of heart-light that filled the heart
更新した理由の連続が
A series of reasons updated
響き合って未来を連れてくる
Echoing together, bringing the future
一千万年一度の霧のサプライズで ロマンチックなキスにしよう
With a once-in-ten-million-years mist surprise, let's make it a romantic kiss
こんばんはー！
Good evening!
いやー熱いですね福岡も！
Man, Fukuoka's hot too!
元気ですかー！
How are you guys doing?!
はい。ということで... 星街すいせいの...
Yes. So... Suisei's...
彗星の如く現れたスターの原石！
A rough diamond of a star that appeared like a comet!
バーチャルアイドルの星街すいせいです！
I'm the virtual idol, Hoshimachi Suisei!
すいちゃんはー？
Sui-chan is...?
今日も可愛いー！
Today, too, is cute!
溜めてみた。今日は。これで溜めてみた。
I tried building up the tension. Today. I tried holding it back like this.
はい！星街すいせい Live Tour 2024 “Spectra of Nova” へようこそー！
Alright! Welcome to Hoshimachi Suisei Live Tour 2024 "Spectra of Nova"!
はい、なんとツアーもつい最後の場所となってしまいました。
Yes, and so, the tour has finally reached its last location.
そうなんですよ。えー、埼玉...
That's right. Yes, we've been to Saitama...
...大阪、福岡と来て。
...Osaka, and now Fukuoka.
福岡、皆さん、今日が最後なんです。
Everyone in Fukuoka, today is the final day.
最後に来れる皆さん、こんにちは！
To everyone here for the finale, hello!
ちょっと絶妙か。絶妙なMCか。
That was a bit... exquisite? An exquisite MC bit.
はい、えー先日も発表したんですけれども。
Yes, and as announced the other day,
ライブツアーは一旦福岡で終わりつつ、
while the live tour ends here in Fukuoka,
あの、武道館のライブ。実は控えてて。
I actually have a Budokan live coming up.
武道館なんです。すごいよね。
It's at the Budokan. Isn't that amazing?
すごいよね。いや本当にそうなんですよね。
It is amazing, right? Yeah, it really is.
すごい。本で、新しいアルバムも出ちゃったりなんかしちゃって。
Incredible. And also, a new album is coming out soon.
そう、さっき歌ったね、“Awake” も新しい3rdアルバムに、
Yes, the song I just sang, "Awake", is also included in the new 3rd album.
あの、入る曲なんですけれども。いっぱいね、聞いてほしいから買ってほしいなー！
I want many people to hear it, so please buy it!
買った！もう予約してくれてる人いっぱい。ありがとうございます。
You bought it? Many of you have already pre-ordered. Thank you so much.
そして、今回も前回と同じく
And just like last time,
バンドメンバーの皆さんを引き連れております。みんな！
I'm accompanied by the band members. Everyone!
えー私、あの、さっきまで実は、
Actually, until just a moment ago,
あの、しらけんのね、控え室にお邪魔して。
I was visiting the Shiraken waiting room,
ギリギリまでルービックキューブやってた。
and I was playing Rubik's Cube until the very last minute.
あ、可愛い？そうだよね。可愛いからいいか。
Oh, it's cute? I thought so. Since it's cute, it's fine.
それでね、ルービックキューブが下手すぎて、
But I'm so bad at Rubik's Cube that
あの、ふーたんにね、“ここは、こうして、こう回して、
Fuu-tan was like, "Do this, turn it like this,
そしたらこうだよ” って。んーんーんー。
and then it'll be like this." I was going "Uhh, uhh, uhh..."
ってやってたら “やめて！カエル化しちゃう！これから歌うんでしょ？” って言われました。
and she said, "Stop! You're giving me the ick! You're about to go sing, aren't you?"
可愛いからいいか！ということで、
Since it's cute, it's fine! Anyway,
そんな可愛いすいちゃんを思う存分見れる推しカメラがあります！
there's a Focus Camera where you can watch cute Sui-chan to your heart's content!
そう、この推しカメラは、あの、ここに残念ながら来られなかった配信の皆さんの特権です！
Yes, this Focus Camera is a privilege for the streaming viewers who unfortunately couldn't be here in person!
見てるよー。ありがとう。
I'm watching you! Thank you.
コメントも読んじゃおうかな。ここら辺に何か宙に浮いてるコメントがね、うーん。
Maybe I'll read some comments. There are comments floating in the air around here...
イエーイ、やったぜ、見えてんでー。
Yay, we did it! We can see you!
釣り席、うわーい、俺らの特権イエーイ、言ってますね。
"Fishing seats", "Yay, our privilege, yay!" they're saying.
そしてなんと、えー韓国でのライブビューイングも行っています。
And surprisingly, we're also doing a live viewing in Korea.
みんな一緒に、アニョハセヨー！
Everyone together, "Annyeonghaseyo"!
いやこれ感動するでしょう、韓国の皆さん。“今俺たちに向けて言ったぞ” つって。
Man, the Korean fans must be moved. Like, "She just said that to us!"
嬉しいですね、色んなね、世界の方が見てくださってると。
It's so nice to have people from all over the world watching.
え、ちなみに今日、
By the way,
海外から来ましたってこと、人？
is there anyone here who came from overseas today?
すごい、いっぱい居なくない？
Wow, aren't there a lot of people?
もう一回、海外から来たって人！
One more time, who came from overseas?!
うっわ、すごい、いっぱい居るじゃん。すごいくね？
Whoa, amazing, there are so many! Isn't that incredible?
え、あの、福岡から来ましたって人！
Uh, who here came from Fukuoka?!
え、福岡県民ですって人！え、多くね？
Wait, who's a Fukuoka resident? There's a lot?!
え、こんなに居るの？福岡県民。すごいくね？
Are there really this many locals? Isn't that amazing?
居るよーって言った今誰か。
Someone just said "We're here!".
え、っと、じゃあ、最後に
Uh, well, finally,
福岡県民でも海外の人でもない人！
anyone who's neither from Fukuoka nor overseas!
あー、居る居る。全然居るわ。じゃあ結構なんかこう、半、半、半くらいなんだね。
Ah, I see you. Plenty of people. So it's like a third, a third, and a third.
いや嬉しいですね。
I'm so happy.
ということで、えーライブの感想はハッシュタグ #駆け巡る星街 でたくさんポスト...
Anyway, please share your thoughts on the concert using the hashtag #駆け巡る星街 and post...
台本いつまでポストなん？
How long is the script going to say "post"?
ツイートだよね！ツイートだよね！
It's "tweet", right?! It's "tweet"!
ツイートしてくださいってことで
So, please tweet about it.
今回はスマホを持ってきました。
This time, I brought my smartphone.
スマホでね、ちょっとね、Twitterで
With my smartphone, you know, on Twitter,
ツイートをね、エゴサしてみたいなって思ってるんです。
I'm thinking of egosearching some tweets.
ちょっとMCの時間がカツカツなんだけど、私が喋りすぎて。
The MC time is a bit tight because I talked too much.
えっと……
Let's see...
何々？
What's this?
星街すいせい 210円。
Hoshimachi Suisei 210 yen.
何々？
What's this?
なんか……え、これ何駅？
Like... wait, what station is this?
何駅でこうなってたの？
At what station was it like this?
あ、博多駅なんだ。
Ah, it's Hakata Station.
博多駅で星街すいせいの、え、ライブ会場最寄り駅まで
At Hakata Station, there's a poster saying it's
210円ですっていうのがすごい分かりやすい貼り紙が貼ってあったっていうね。
210 yen to the venue's nearest station, which is very helpful.
あ、貼ったよ？
Ah, "I put it up"?
お前が貼ったの！？
Did you put it up!?
あ、買ったよか。買ったよね。
Oh, "I bought it"? You bought it, right.
あと、あの、我らが協賛のふくやさんが
Also, um, our sponsor Fukuya...
なんかどっかで明太子売ってたって聞いた。
...I heard they were selling mentaiko somewhere.
買った？
Did you buy some?
買ってくれました！
They bought it!
絶対に全員買いなさい。
Absolutely everyone, go buy some.
絶対に全員食べなさい。
Absolutely everyone, go eat it.
本当に美味しいから。なんかね、なんかその、空港のところとか
It's really delicious. Also, at the airport and such,
なんかね、地下街店とかなんかいろんなところで
at the underground mall and various other places,
「星詠みの皆様ようこそ福岡へ」って書いてあるの。
it says "Welcome to Fukuoka, Hoshiyomi."
凄くない？
Isn't that amazing?
見に行ってくださいね。
Please go and see it.
はい、えっと「巻いてください」というね、ジェスチャーが出ましたので
Okay, um, I just got the "wrap it up" gesture,
巻いてまいりますよ。
so I'll wrap things up.
え、無料チラ見せについてYouTube、TikTokでご覧の方はここまでです。
That's it for those watching the free preview on YouTube and TikTok.
まだまだ一緒に盛り上がりたい皆様は概要欄から配信サイトへ行って、
If you want to keep hyping with us, go to the streaming site from the description
チケットを買ってください。
and buy a ticket.
みんな、もう一回「エ」を。
Everyone, one more "A."
もう一回「エ」をください。
Please give me one more "A."
せーの！
Ready, go!
エ！
A!
代わりにね、言っときましょう。はい。
I'll say it for them. Yes.
それでは次の曲は何の曲が来るのかな？
Well then, I wonder what the next song will be?
お楽しみに！
Look forward to it!
無料パートは終了いたしました
ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The sneak peek part of the show has ended.
Thank you for watching!
無料パートは終了いたしました
The sneak peek part of the show has ended.
ご視聴ありがとうございました！
Thank you for watching!